{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain runs on the Fox Engine.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of &quot;Doomhammer&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Donald Duck played the role of Bob Cratchit in Disney&#039;s 1983 adaptation of A Christmas Carol.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}